I'm on a journey out to see
the world While I'm on my own,
I've yet to reach the end So won't
you come along with me right now?
Surely then we can!
Follow me now as we
journey on from sea to sea
For that treasure known
by everybody as one piece.
Even though they laugh and
say it's just a fantasy.
We are going, there's no doubt we go.
Cause we can feel the
rush of energy overcome.
It will lead the way.
Keep pretending that you know what to do.
Books will only get in the way.
No guides for today.
Do not worry soon, the rain
will be gone with the wind.
Keep your chin up, raise the
anchor, now that's what you'll do.
Give it time and calm the storm
that you have built within.
Come and have my board at number two.
Once tomorrow's wind picks up,
we set stuff cause we can't.
Thresh enough, stand tall and
take a look at one of you.
All the journey makes
me wanna see somebody.
There are things out there
you just won't believe.
Beyond your wildest dreams.
Don't think for a second.
It's not the truth.
That's the story most will believe.
Not me, come and see.
I am on a journey out to see.
The world done on my own.
I've got my group of friends.
Together we've got our way.
That's how it's done.
Says your captain.
Who says it can't be done?
We haven't even tried.
Gotta just believe we'll
make it to the end.
I just wanna do it all right now.
Together surely we can.
Yes, we can.
You can.
Just take this moment in.
We can.
I can.
Just take this feeling in.
Right now.
Oh yes, we can.
Yes, we can!
Come on!
I want to see some more
ninja moves! Neen, neen!
That's enough!
Neen, neen for a lifetime!
What you saw was not meant to be seen.
Oh, really?
But you were putting on a show.
Peaceful, not her.
Oh.
Huh?
You guys okay?
You're crying.
Do not be absurd.
Men from 1.0 never cry.
But my heart weep because
this beautiful land
was not in such a sorry
state when I arrived.
The streets were bustling with life.
Smiles shone on the people's faces.
The country was overflowing with life.
This was too much.
I am unworthy of such loyalty.
But I vow to avenge you and repay
the kindness you've shown me.
So I pray you will forgive me!
Hey, Yugara! Good news!
Seems the deciphering
of the stone is done.
Come back inside the whale.
Well, Nami?
You got all this information
from the Poneglyph, huh?
With this data, I can
draw up a nautical chart.
Then we can pinpoint the
location of something, I'm sure.
This stone has a special name.
It's a road Poneglyph.
As you, Karoo, know,
all of the major players are searching
for the end point of the Grand Line.
That stone is a guide to get there.
That's why the whale forest is held
to be sacred by the Mink tribe,
and why us guardians are sworn
to protect it no matter the cost.
The end of the Grand
Line is within our grasp.
It's a guide to the final
island, to Laugh-Tail?
Precisely so.
However...
That's a big deal!
If I go there, I'll be
king of the pirates! Ah!
Finally!
We can do it!
Laugh-Tail at last!
It's just like that
flower-head guy told us.
All we needed was this
red thing all along.
Calm down, there's more.
Just, uh, let me finish.
This stone here isn't
the only red pony glyph.
There are four, in fact.
There are four left, too!
That's crazy! Idiot!
Just let the dog talk
The stone does provide a location But
the coordinates, at least on their own,
do not point to Laugh Tale itself.
The other three road
poneglyphs provide the same.
Coordinates to different places.
However,
when you, Karoo, have determined
all four of those locations,
then connect the points on a map,
their true purpose will be apparent.
Where the points cross,
you, Karoo, will find the final island!
which was only reached once by
the King of the Pirates long ago.
Laugh Tale at last.
It's closer than I thought!
The final island!
Once we get there, we'll know the truth.
Is it actually real or just a legend?
The One Piece.
OK, it's time to go.
Can't go where exactly?
It's kind of a big world.
We'll get Sanji, then
we'll get the One Piece.
You're going to do that all on your own?
Or what?
Honestly,
if you gotta travel to Whole
Cake Island with Peccoms,
that might actually help us
kill two birds with one stone.
As I mentioned, there
are four road poneglyphs.
We know the location of three of them.
One's right here, of course.
And two under the control of
pirates, and powerful ones at that.
Go figure.
Big Mom's the first one on the list.
And the second another emperor
kaido king of the beasts.
So we just gotta rob him, yeah?
I can't believe it.
I feel like all I can see
in front of me is darkness.
Yeah, I can relate. Bring it on.
I'll fight both of them at once.
We gotta kick their butt sooner or later.
There's some sensitivity here.
I wasn't ready for all of
this to happen so soon.
And it's scary as hell.
Okay, don't think I won't pee my pants
because I totally will, damn straight.
I'll pee my pants too.
So watch out.
Hold on.
You gotta don't need to steal
the poneglyphs or anything.
Reckless like that?
Huh, we don't.
How are you gonna gonna lug
around a stone that size anyway?
Just take an etching or whatever.
then translate it once you're safe.
Aha, I see.
We'll just sneak into Big
Mom's and Kaido's hideouts,
avoid any dangerous confrontations!
make a copy, and then bam!
Then we'll sell straight to Laugh
Tale before they know any better.
And you'll be king of the
pirates, and everyone is happy!
You think that face is
a good plan, you jerk!
Oh, it's lame and weak!
I want to kick butt and be manly!
Surprise, hearty, straight here!
You're right, you guys!
But you're the one I'm worried about.
This could get rather tricky, Nico Robin.
Those who are interested in the blank
century are also hunting down pornoglyphs.
and recording their data.
Right now, that's all fine and good,
but the problem is that none of them can
actually read the text
even if they find it.
So what happens when all those
big shots hit a dead end?
They're likely going to kidnap the
only person capable of reading them.
Namely, you gotta...
What?
Kidnap Robin? Hell no!
I'm not worried.
My friends are strong.
I know they'll protect me
no matter what may happen.
Oh, Robin, you don't have
to flatter me like that.
I'm glad to help.
I'll kick butt for you any old time.
I mean, I'm only kind of strong.
I vow to protect you with my life
and my life after death as well.
I will do anything to protect Robin.
She's super!
No one is laying a finger on Robin!
Or I'll take their lives and their money.
It sounds like they've
got things covered, then.
You're lucky to have
such reliable friends.
By the way, why do the Minx happen to be
so knowledgeable about the Poneglyphs?
We have our old lord
to thank for that one.
You see, Kozuki Oden had a
great interest in the stones.
It's only natural,
considering his history.
The story is...
Hey, Mutt, is it alright for
me to tell them all this stuff?
Yes, you may proceed.
They are allies, and they are trustworthy.
We need not keep secrets.
The deal is the Kozuki clan
from the land of Wano is a
family of talented stonemasons
and has been for generations
In fact this very day.
They're still probably the
best in the world stonemasons
Since long back 800 years or so at least
They used their talents to construct stone
documents that could not be destroyed.
In other words, they made the Poneglyphs.
The Kozuki clan.
All the stones were made by them?
And I never knew.
You made those rocks that Robin likes?
I doubt it.
Of course not, you fool.
He was my ancestors from many years ago.
Then do you know what they say?
Because that would be real handy.
I'm afraid that such details
were not passed on to us.
You'll simply have to
read them as was intended.
The only thing passed down is
the method to decipher the text.
But even that...
It is a most tragic tale.
Before the method could be
taught to Lord Momonosuke,
His father Kozuki Odin met
an exceedingly cruel fate.
By cruel fate you mean to say
that Momonosuke's father is dead?
Indeed Lord Odin is gone.
And Wano is?
Wano, it's...
My name is Odin, and I was born to boil!
Hey, you guys, if this is too hard,
you don't have to talk about it.
Lord Odin was executed by
order of the Shogun of Wano,
who is in an alliance
with the pirate Kaido.
Yet he faced his demise willingly,
with courage, in order to
save all of his retainers.
He fought with Kaido?
This runs deep.
Even today, the foul Emperor
Kaido and his beast pirate crew
You are still in one of them.
So you can't go back home.
Look, I'm not trying to
twist the knife here.
But why was this lord of yours
executed in the first place?
Is that why you have to hide?
Why you've got people hunting you down?
Indeed, it is as you say.
We are being pursued because of the grievous
crime that our lord was charged with.
But Kaido doesn't want our lives.
Rather, he wants to pry
information out of us.
For Lord Odin, who was
the previous Daimyo.
Sailed the seas with the pirate Gold D.
Roger And gazed upon the
final island: Laugh Tale.
And there he witnessed the secrets
of the world with his own eyes?
What?
Momo's dad was on Roger's crew.
So the lord of these samurai,
he made it to Laugh Tale.
That's a big deal.
Why didn't you tell us any of that stuff?
A man who learned the world's secrets,
probably alongside Rayleigh.
Yes, we know.
We learned all of it.
the entirety of the missing history.
So you're saying that Kaido was
using Doflamingo and Caesar to
try and learn these secrets of
the world or whatever from you?
since you guys were Odin's servants?
Yes, that's correct, Sorzoro.
We know nothing on this subject matter.
Lord Odin made certain not to
burden us with any secrets.
Therefore, we possess no knowledge of it.
Admittedly, if we were familiar with
it, we would not dare tell a soul.
Whether we know it or not,
we'll always be pursued.
That having been said, it leaves us with
just one choice, and that is to fight.
His final message before his
departure were these simple words.
Do it for me.
Open Wano's borders.
But why would he ask for that?
The land of Wano was
sealed from the world.
How shameful that our duty
was to protect Lord Odin.
And yet, in the end,
it was he who saved us.
Now we must go on with
this terrible disgrace.
We have shamed ourselves.
Our only solution is to ensure that
our master's dying wish is carried out.
We must kill the current
Shogun of Wano and
open the closed borders
of our dear country.
Achieving said feat is our deepest desire.
Yet we're in a quandary.
Due to the combined strength
of the Shogun and Kaido.
Wano's stuck in a Loguetown.
Back at home, the seeds of
rebellion are slowly being sown.
Yet we fall short.
Our numbers are lacking as of yet.
And our victory is a distant hope.
I see quite the dilemma.
Still we all must win.
Which is why in order to search
for allies that might assist us.
We turned our attention to the sea.
Our initial destination was to be Zo.
Yes, he speaks of our special bond.
The Kozuki clan and the Mink
tribe have been aligned for ages.
And swore a pact to join our fates as one.
Above all else, me and the mutt here
were Lord Odin's direct vassals.
Ever since Raizo showed up,
every one of our soldiers were
prepared for an inevitable war.
However, we underestimated the enemy.
It only took one of Kaido's troops
to leave us in this main state.
Jack alone was too much for us.
An embarrassing reality.
Boy, you're a disgrace, I know.
Hey, they pulled a dirty trick on you.
There's no need to beat yourself up.
Yeah,
how could you have possibly known they
were going to use that awful poison gas?
Alas, sportsmanship
does not apply to wars.
No matter how vicious their game
plan, this is still our home country.
There are no excuses.
We shall not make the
same mistake next time.
From now on, we'll be prepared.
They shall soon realize.
They've yet to see our full potential as
we still have one final ace up our sleeve.
We have a request of you, Sir Luffy.
And you, Sir Law.
It pains me greatly to ask a favor
after you have saved our lives.
But your strength has astounded
me time and time again.
Undesperate, Sir Luffy, we need you.
As well as your crew, I beg you,
help us slay the Shogun of Wano and
strike down Kaido of the Four Emperors.
Whoa! Alright!
I'm all about this kind of alliance.
The Samurai and the Meek Tribe?
Now that's a lot of power at our disposal.
I mean, we were gonna kick Kaido's
ass sooner or later, right?
Yeah, we gotta get in on this.
They have a ninja! Yeah!
I refuse.
Come on, man!
But they are friends, aren't they?
Do you need me to walk you
through why this is a good idea?
You can't pass this off!
Let's not rush into a no!
This is about unity!
I'm gonna talk some sense into my buddy,
so could you give me a few minutes?
Stop it!
Luffy, you should accept.
Or else we'll lose all
our respect for you.
Hold up.
I think that Luffy
actually has a point here.
Mommy?
After all, we should negotiate.
Hurry, don't you dare!
What are you?
A figurehead? Huh, Momo?
Knock it off!
You're in charge, right?
Aren't you the leader of these guys?
Say something already!
You just gonna cry?
You're making him cry!
Stop yelling at him, you big bully!
Now, now, Luffy.
You're expecting far too much of him.
Heirs don't typically take
over the responsibilities
of leadership until they come of age.
Perhaps it's best if we
let the adults confer.
Oh, Momonosuke?
That's right, sweet little Momo.
Come here.
I'm sorry.
Our idiot captain likes to
run his mouth sometimes.
Gaze out upon it, Momonosuke.
This is the world, wider
than your imagination.
Father, I...
We're surrounded, I fear!
Father, help!
Ready the flaming arrows!
You must flee!
Follow the escape route!
Everyone, vacate!
Your father truly is?
A fool of a lord.
I want to vanquish Everikido!
He was an enemy to both of my parents!
And also responsible for
their untimely deaths!
I want nothing more than to
grow up and become strong so
that I may one day smite him
and avenge my mother and father!
I wish to protect my
loyal servants as well!
Lord Momonosuke!
This little guy's grit,
he's moved me to tears.
You Karoo are soft in your old age.
Shut your muzzle!
However, I'm powerless.
I'm too small to assist in battle.
That's why I must ask, will
you please help me fight?
Please loopy, I beg of you!
That's more like it.
Hey, Momo.
Let's team up.
Just leave Kaido to me.
And it's an alliance.
Thank you from the bottom of my heart.
I am unworthy of such kindness.
No, that's all wrong.
Grab it tight like this. Go bam.
I cannot thank you enough.
Come on, with more oomph.
I am grabbing your hand.
No, this way.
I now see the point he was making.
Go-roo-nya-nya-nya!
An alliance is born.
Let's break out the booze and party.
Hey, Straw Hat. Hmm?
You should have run this by me first.
It's cool, right?
It is, but still, how alleviating.
Perhaps we should reflect
upon our attitudes. Huh?
We were guilty of infantilizing him,
but he is the head of the Kozuki clan,
is he not?
Our drive to protect him had us
overlooking something so vital.
True, Sir Luffy butted heads with a child.
But remarkably, he also gave
him the courage to be a man.
He is truly amazing.
True indeed.
I now understand your
respect for this pirate. Hmm.
Okay.
Let's gather around.
Come on, everyone!
Are we all ready?
We're gonna kick Emperor
Kaido's ass together!
It's Zero, the Ninja Pirate
Mink Samurai Alliance!
That's a mouthful.
Do we need the ninja part?
Of course we do!
Okay, jeez.
The target's Kaido!
Let's do this!
Dogstorm, Catviper, Momo, Kin'emon,
Kanjuro, Ninja Guy, and Traffy!
I don't know anything about Kaido, but
with an alliance like this, he's toast.
This is gonna be fun!
By the way, don't you ever
bow your heads to me again.
And don't kneel.
Us being allies means...
we're best friends, too!
We are not!
But if we're working together,
there is one condition. Hmm.
Hmm? Hang on.
Perhaps that should have been
mentioned to us beforehand.
What's the condition?
Before we go anywhere, my
crew's down a man right now.
Gotcha.
This is about Sanji.
What happened?
I'm afraid that is a long story.
Yugara?
Mean the Big Mom?
Why didn't you tell me?
It all went down while
Yugara were napping.
I'm gonna run off and
rescue him real quick.
So hold off on fighting until I get back.
Huh, that's your only condition.
Well, if that's all, then
we shall gladly stand by.
Thank you.
And he's as strong as a thousand people.
Trust me when I say this'll be worth it.
Then I'm worth 2,000 people.
Of course you are.
I see, then.
He'd be quite the asset.
However, take precaution.
This is Big Mom.
I'm not planning on fighting her,
and besides, I'll take Lion Viper.
Wait, what?
Who is that?
Nyah-ha-ha-ha!
Lion Viper?
Nyah-ha-ha!
The miracles never cease
today, do they? No joke.
We couldn't predict this.
Those two had a rivalry so
strong they found it easier
to split the day in half
rather than see each other,
but they have finally settled
their differences—hard
to believe—the moment has finally come,
and we're here to witness it.
Supposedly, master Cat Viper and Duke
Dogstorm are once an inseparable pair;
however, one day they came back
from a long voyage, barely alive.
barely alive
And it was like they had been
fighting all their lives.
Any time they even shared a glance,
it would cause an altercation.
What could have happened between them?
All that happened before
I was born, right?
That'd be correct.
Pager and I were only little children when
those two returned from their journey.
Our two kings are friends again.
Let's throw a big feast!
Now we can wake up or go to
sleep whenever we please!
We have confirmation on
the target, Master Jack!
You think I can't see it?
It's huge!
Damn it.
I think I'd have to come back here.
Sheep's head,
I didn't expect you to return to me and
report that Rhizo was not on the island.
The Ming tribe is quite hardy. Tell me,
what would happen if
those who escaped the gas
were able to nurse the
others back to health?
That idiot better keep his mouth shut.
If Master Jack finds out that they
survived and we got our asses handed to us,
then we're screwed.
When someone's on the brink of death,
you have to see it all the way through.
Mercy only breeds vengeance.
There's no need to worry, Master.
If they're already
weakened, this'll be easy.
We'll put the stragglers
out of their misery.
That won't be necessary.
We'll kill the elephant.
Thank you.